Previously on The Chi...
Where Trinity at?
You need to tell your bitch
to mind
her own fucking business.
Chill.
Bitch. don't forget
I ain't scared to die.
I got something to tell you.
It's messy.
Shit.
Tiff came over the other night.
and she tried to fuck me.
You serious?
And what'd you do?
I turned my back
when she tried to kiss me.
and I-I said
I was in a relationship.
Man. my girl lost our baby
'cause of you!
I fucking hate you!
Man. get the fuck
out my house. nigga.
Man. you gotta go. man.
Dramatic music
This one is one
of our more seasoned artists.
which is why it's
a little bit more expensive.
It's amazing.
People love a politician
with a baby on the way.
Good luck with that.
Stranger things have happened.
So now you wanna be for real?
Anything's possible.
- I'm not a fetish.
- I know that.
If you walk out that door
and continue to live a lie.
then I don't want you
to come back.
We are not having a big wedding.
So what do you want?
I want something small and...
intimate.
You keep my daughter's name
out your mouth.
Do you hear me?
Look. if Victor's
gonna be the light.
I have to manage the darkness.
Or you can let Q do that.
No. I'ma put that old
motherfucker out of his misery.
He's my son's father. Otis.
Yeah. but your son's gone.
You're early. young blood.
Any reason you wanted
to get there so quick...
The Undisputed Truth's
"Smiling Faces Sometimes"
Smiling faces
Sometimes
Pretend to be your friend
Smiling faces
Show no traces
Of the evil that lurks within
Can you dig it
Smiling faces. smiling faces
Sometimes
they don't tell the truth
Smiling faces. smiling faces
Tell lies...
Oh. yeah
The fuck is that?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Let me tell you
The truth is in the eyes
'Cause the eyes don't lie
Amen
Remember. a smile
is just a frown
Turned upside down
My friend
So hear me when I'm saying
Smiling faces. smiling faces...
They don't tell the truth...
tense music
This motherfucker.
What the fuck you got me into?
I just needed somebody
to help me dump the body.
- That's all.
- That's all?
Nigga. I'm running for office.
and you couldn't call
nobody else?
Yes. I could've called
somebody else.
but you're the only person
I know
that got something to lose.
Drive.
No.
Victor...
...you only get to be
who you are in the light
because of what I fucking do
in the dark.
Drive.
Dramatic jazz music
"I am Saturday mornings
in the summertime.
I am two bounces
and a front flip
off the diving board.
I'm hilarious."
Together let's run away...
"I am a brother.
a son. a nephew.
a favorite cousin. a grandson."
I see it. I see it.
Where's the other L?
Where's the capital L?
- I see it.
- Ooh. do the happy dance.
Emmett Junior.
We ain't gotta talk about it
if you don't want to.
Yeah. can we just forget
about it?
I can try. but we can't act
like that shit didn't happen.
I know.
That's why I told Rob.
and we had a real conversation
about it.
Yeah. I told Kiesha too.
Great. so everybody
know my business.
I'm not trying to be messy.
I was just trying
to be an honest man.
You ain't gotta be honest
about everything. nigga.
Yeah. I do.
This the new me.
I-I'ma tell her everything.
- So now you Mr. Honesty?
- Yes.
Okay. then.
I'm happy to hear
you came clean too.
Yeah. I like being open.
I know.
Not like that.
I know what you meant.
I can't lie.
I never thought we'd be here.
Yeah. me either.
It feels better. though. right?
Yeah. it does.
Yeah.
- A'ight. then.
- Sure.
I'ma step out.
Oh. don't forget
we got a parent-teacher
conference tomorrow.
I got it.
It's on my calendar.
Oh. so now
you got a calendar too?
Oh. yeah. I told you.
I'm a new man.
Come on. Tiff.
- I'm on it.
- Bye.
How much you think I got?
Mm. about...
2.000?
Okay. how much
you got right now?
I counted it last night.
That's 4.000.
Think I got enough
for my own spot?
I don't know.
Why?
Why not?
Don't you wanna be on your own?
I mean. I never
really thought about it.
Shit. I think about it
all the time.
Can't wait
to leave my mama's crib.
You're almost 18.
You'll be out soon.
Yeah. but...
I got the money to do it now.
Your parents are not
gonna let you do that.
Well. I'll get emancipated.
You really gon' take
your parents to court?
You're putting me
in real danger.
I'm keeping danger at bay.
- Not by killing Q.
- Shit. I had to.
That motherfucker
was losing his mind.
And yours is intact?
My goal...
is protect your dumb ass.
Tracy.
the ROCK center.
and Trinity House.
You're putting us all at risk.
I need you to go back in hiding.
Let me take things
from here. please.
I just can't leave Tracy.
Fool. if you not careful.
you gon' get her killed.
And I refuse to let that happen.
So you the big man now?
Somebody gotta be.
Stay away from her.
Even when I'm tired
in the morning...
Breathe deep.
Open your mind.
Never on the sight
in the morning
You always get me right
I'm so thankful
for the morning...
Let your breath untie the knots
in your body and your mind.
Oh. thank y'all for doing this.
Anything
for the beautiful bride.
Yeah. thank you
for inviting me. Jada.
This is amazing.
I still can't believe
you and Darnell
are actually getting married.
Hey. old love
rekindles sometimes. okay?
The jury's still out
on you and Emmett.
I think Emmett
has really changed.
Babe. if I can give you
a second chance.
we can give Emmett
I didn't wanna say nothing.
My stuff need not
be brought into this.
- And why not?
- Because I'm married.
That don't make it no better.
Okay. let's just all
take a deep breath.
I agree.
Great work. ladies.
Jada. you gonna ever tell me
why I didn't get a plus-one?
I didn't want any shenanigans
at my wedding.
Otis isn't all bad.
I don't know Otis like that.
Well. how you gon'
get to know him
if you won't let me bring him
to your wedding?
How 'bout we...
go on a double date
after the honeymoon?
I'd like that.
We could join y'all
if you wanna triple.
I'd love that.
Are you saying that
'cause you want a buffer?
I'm saying that
because the more. the merrier.
Keep breathing.
Yes. just like that.
Fucking Victor.
So you're an accomplice.
- I didn't have a choice.
- Doesn't matter.
You still got blood
on your hands.
Fuck!
- Does Tracy know?
- Course not.
Do you wanna tell her?
I can't. man. 'cause then
I have to tell her I helped.
and that would kill her.
So what do you wanna do?
I wanna give her the tape.
And what you think
that's gonna do.
make her fall
out of love with him?
- I hope so.
- It's not enough
just for her to see it.
You need everyone to see it.
Is that your way
of getting revenge?
It's my way of making sure he
goes away for good this time.
Hmm.
So when do you wanna
drop the tape?
I'll give you a signal.
I got you.
And I think I'm gonna need you
on my team.
You asking me
to join your campaign?
Would you say yes?
Depends on the offer.
I might just make you one.
You know we gon' have
to flip that. right?
You know this dude?
Yeah. tall dude
named Rob. Q's nephew.
Q was getting him weed
from a plug out in Cali.
Rob.
Sounds like a good business.
It is.
He been making money for us
hand over fist.
Was he close with Q?
Not really. he ain't really
rock with his family like that.
and the relationship with him
and Q was mostly business.
Hmm.
You know what?
I want you to pay him a visit.
Let him know
that his uncle's dead
but that his weed business
is very much alive.
A'ight. bet.
Dramatic hip-hop music
Okay. so I'm gonna
get you a new producer.
some studio time.
and you should have an EP out
in the next few months.
And where are you getting
the money
to pay for all this?
I'll figure it out.
How?
I'm gonna reach out
to a few people
and see if they wanna invest
in your future.
Who?
I don't really wanna
give out my contacts yet.
That's 'cause
your ass ain't got any.
It's not funny.
Just give me some time.
How much time?
Ma is ha. I got you.
You better.
Don't be playing
with my feelings.
Got bank. got drank. got tree
They know who we are.
we ain't showing ID
They don't really
make 'em like me
Whipping and I'm dripping
on 'em like an IV
Got bank. got drank. got tree...
Hey. oh. with the hand.
Oh. his granny right there.
Ah. slap shot at Granny.
Is that that nigga Trig?
Oh. I ain't never...
Tense music
Get your bitch ass
out the car. nigga.
Don't do that.
Don't even do that shit.
Nigga. try me.
Can't live with regrets
Life is a game.
you gotta play it like chess
I been taken for granted.
somebody gotta get checked
I took so many Ls. that
means I gotta get blessed
I been working on self.
I was bad in my prime
If you had to get yours.
that means I had...
You got it.
Yeah. I know
I fucking got it. nigga.
Move the fuck around.
I thought my talent would
take me out the hood
They overlooked me.
I'm still feeling like that
I got my feelings attached...
Bitch-ass nigga.
Don't give up.
we got the lives to impact
But who looking at me
Ain't nobody come around
when I was looking at three
Bad time. you niggas
sleep on me like bedtime
I can't wait till my name
is the headliner
Till then. fuck everybody
Hey. Mrs. Robinson.
Hey.
I'm not your wife just yet.
Woman. you been mine ever since
I first laid my eyes on you.
Mm-hmm.
So. uh. we good on the venue?
Oh. yeah. we real good.
Mm-hmm.
You write your vows out yet?
Yup. and they
real emotional too.
You better not be
quoting the O'Jays.
What? Why not?
Darnell. come on.
I want you to be serious.
Oh. woman. I'ma be real serious.
I'm speaking
straight from my heart.
- so don't worry.
- Hey. hey. I told you.
no more sex
until after we get married.
- Wait. you for real?
- Yeah. I'm for real.
I want our day
to be extra special.
- Yeah. I got your extra...
- Mm.
...and that special too.
Wait. let me see you walk away
from me again.
Stop it.
How you. uh. feeling
about the announcement?
Confident.
- Good.
- Mm.
I'm sure everything
will go as planned.
Thanks for agreeing to come.
Well. I have
to cover it for work.
Mm.
Is that the only reason
you're coming?
Look.
After you announce.
I'm going to leave the city.
What do you mean?
I don't have a reason to stay.
Wait. I-I thought
we were building something.
You're building something.
And I am happy for you.
But I need
to find my happiness too.
So... this is it for us?
I can't spend my life
waiting for you to...
find yourself.
I know you hear me
I know it's best.
I'm saying that
Boy. we could be the big picture
Know they put us
on their mood boards
And wallpapers. real. baby
All you needed was the sugar
All you needed was
the sugar. honey. iced tea
I think you should
tell Victor what happened.
Nah. he-he don't
need that right now.
What?
You would have died
if Bakari wasn't there.
That would've been a'ight.
Just-just promise me
you'll be safe.
I can't make that promise.
I mean... shit goes down.
I just...
can't get caught slipping again.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
Okay. well... I gotta go.
Where you going?
I gotta figure out
how to make some money.
Ain't your daddy rich?
I mean. we do well.
but he's just not gonna give me
a bunch of money.
Then what's the point
of having it?
I wanna earn it on my own.
And how you gon' do that?
You think Smokey's is hiring?
Stop laughing.
Like. I'm serious.
I don't know.
Ask Papa.
Are you all here for EJ?
Yeah.
EJ's made a lot of progress
since our last meeting.
Tss. that's what
I'm talking about.
But the battle
isn't over just yet.
I wanna enroll EJ
in something called
an individualized
education program.
What's that?
I learned about that in school.
It just means they'll make
special accommodations
and give him extra attention.
right?
Yeah. he'll have a whole team
of people to help him
focus on his reading
and give him emotional support.
Yeah. and EJ can learn
at his own pace
and not feel like something's
wrong with him. you know?
Are you in education?
No. no. I took a few early
childhood development classes.
and I do flash cards with EJ
all the time.
He loves it.
We do. like. a victory dance
whenever he gets
an answer right.
- Positive reinforcement...
- Yeah.
...goes a long way. so...
It really does take a village.
and this looks like
a really good one.
You should be very proud.
All right.
Thank you. Ms. Green.
Nice seeing you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey. uh.
we have a teacher's aide
position opening up.
You should apply for it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean. you seem like
you're really passionate
about kids and their well-being.
It's what we need around here.
Maybe I will.
Hey. can we talk?
I just wanted to say thank you.
I can tell you really care
about my son.
Of course.
And I also owe you an apology.
I shouldn't have tried
to push up on Emmett.
Why did you do it?
I think I was jealous.
You still want him?
No. I just tried to see
if I could still pull him.
and I guess I can't.
Well. I'm sorry
I didn't tell you right away.
It's cool.
We even now?
We better be.
You forgive me?
I guess so.
I can't believe
you back with Emmett again.
Girl. me either.
Well. at least
I can trust you with my son.
And can I trust you with my man?
Girl. I'm good.
That was his last chance. okay?
I'm so glad he behaved.
Honestly. so am I.
Girl. that would have been
a mess.
Hey. we good?
Yeah. we good. bro.
Cool.
All right. so you'll be
on bathroom and trash duty.
Um. why can't I
work the register?
'Cause you just started.
Papa. I'm not really good
with smelly jobs.
Look. if you can't handle it.
let me know now.
'cause I got a lot
of cousins out here
that's looking for paper.
Fine. I'll do it.
- Come on.
- God.
And fix your attitude.
The streets keep calling.
I can't stay away
Plus. the team counting
on me now to make a play
For all the days that I was down
I'ma make 'em pay...
Who did this?
Me. nigga.
- Really?
- Yeah.
These are amazing.
I made enough so. uh.
everybody can wear 'em
at your announcement.
Man. you did good. boy.
You like 'em?
Do I like 'em?
Man. come here. bro.
I love 'em.
Love. man.
What?
Yo. hold up.
Yo. Shaad!
Man!
It's been sitting on my spirit
Still won't nothing change
what we came to do
What we came to do
Stack this money to the ceiling
How you feel about me.
I wish the same
Hey.
You should've called.
These are for you.
They're beautiful. but you
still owe me an apology.
I know.
Can I come in?
That depends.
Did you mean what you said
about my son?
No.
And I'll never
let it happen again.
I promise.
Thank you.
What about Q?
Um...
...I found a solution.
I'm gonna step in
for him for a while.
What does that mean?
It means I might have
to lay low again.
What does that mean for us?
I don't know yet.
But what I do know...
...is I don't wanna lose you.
Then don't.
Soft music
So. uh...
I've been meaning
to talk to you.
I need to talk to you too.
- Uh...
- Okay. you go first.
Uh...
I'm glad we worked things out.
you know?
After Valentine's Day.
I been waiting a long time
to find someone like you.
And honestly.
I was about to give up.
But then you sang to me.
and I been falling for you
ever since.
I love the man
that you're becoming.
And I love
what we're building together.
Me too.
So I was wondering
if you wanna move in with me.
Oh. uh...
...wow. uh...
Uh. wait. are you okay?
Is-is-is it too soon?
No. no. that. uh...
Baby.
that's-that's-that's amazing.
- That's... exciting.
- Oh!
So that's a yes?
Hell yeah. Yeah. yeah.
So what were you gonna tell me?
You know what?
Your news is so good.
I totally forgot about mine.
Aww.
Fuck is you doing here?
Hey. your uncle's dead.
How I know you ain't lying?
You know who Douda is?
Know the name.
He gon' give you a call
off a private number.
He'll let you know
the new arrangements.
Who-who killed him. G?
It don't matter.
Where's Q?
Why?
Otis dropped by and mentioned
he found a solution with Q.
- Is that what he said?
- Yeah.
Look. do me a favor.
Stay away from him. okay?
Why?
'Cause there's a lot of shit
he's not telling you.
and I want you to be safe.
We all have our secrets. Victor.
Marcus.
It's time.
Your moms are so nice.
Why you trying
to get away from them?
I just want my freedom.
You'll have it in a year.
Until then.
why can't you just calm down?
You just don't get it. Lynae.
They invade my privacy.
They treat me like a kid.
so I just wanna leave.
be on my own.
So you gon' leave me too?
No.
No. I always got your back.
You know this. but...
...right now. I just...
I feel trapped.
Hey. you two.
Hey. we have some good news.
Your adoption papers
are completed.
All that's left
to do now is sign.
What? You didn't change
your mind. did you?
No.
I'm really happy.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Oh.
Welcome to the family.
We closed.
I know.
I hear that. um.
business is good.
It's been great.
Have you ever thought
about expanding?
Um...
I would. but I ain't got
the money for that just yet.
Yeah. well. you're in luck.
Here. let's have a seat.
Yeah.
You know. I'm. um...
I'm very interested in investing
in a business like yours.
Um. look. I would...
I would love some money. but...
...I wanna know
what-what comes with it.
Hmm. well. I'm not perfect.
but I am good at making money.
Yeah. I can see that.
And I wanna turn Smokey's
into a franchise.
So do I.
Then you need my help.
How much money
you willing to put up?
Oh. man. a lot of money.
A lot.
Can we be more s-specific?
Yeah.
Um. Emmett. right?
How about this?
If you trust me.
I will make you a very rich man.
Hey. yo. where you going?
Deja asked me
to move in with her. man.
Shit!
Congratulations.
Yeah. she a good woman.
Hey. yes. she is.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you. man.
Yeah. you know I'm gonna miss
your crazy ass.
I'ma miss you too. bro.
Man.
Hey. man.
Thanks for never
giving up on me.
Thanks for bringing
me back to life.
Come in.
- Hey. sweetheart.
- Hey.
What you need?
I wanna use my college money
to fund Maisha's career.
Have you lost your mind?
See. this is why
I didn't wanna ask you.
I've been putting money
in that college fund
since you were a baby.
I know.
That money is for you
to get a higher education
and nothing else.
Well. what if I don't want
a higher education?
Are you...
No. I'm not gonna let you
throw your life away.
That's not what I'm doing.
What if this Ma is ha... thing
doesn't work out. huh?
- Then what?
- That's not gonna happen.
Oh. it's a possibility.
Look. I would rather invest
in my dreams
than a piece of paper.
Jemma. a college degree is more
than just a piece of paper.
It represents...
And it's something
that I no longer value.
Hmm.
You're serious about this.
Yes. I am.
Okay.
I will give you a portion
of your college fund. but...
if you don't make something
of yourself in a year.
you gotta go to school.
Deal?
I'll agree to that.
I don't know
what I just got myself into.
Breaking news tonight.
Former Chicago mayor
Otis Perry caught on camera
beating his then chief
of staff. Marcus St. John.
We're only showing you
a portion of this video.
but warning: it is graphic.
Tense music
Some are defending
the mayor's behavior.
while others say his actions
are extremely problematic.
What's wrong
with a man protecting himself?
I'm sure he had his reasons.
You can't be
the mayor of Chicago
acting like that.
And you a Black man too?
Come on. now.
As of now.
Marcus St. John
has remained silent
on the release of the video.
We hope to have more
as this story
continues to break.
Dan. back to you.
God damn it.
You gon' say something?
Nah. I ain't saying shit.
And you know what? I ain't
going no-fucking-where either.
I'm gonna have to lay low
for a bit.
That's smart.
I need somebody to be
my eyes and ears on the street.
Well. shit. that's easy.
I can do that.
No. no. you can't move around
like you used to.
I need somebody young...
and unafraid.
I got just the little young 'un.
What the fuck
we waiting on. man?
That's the little nigga
that pulled a gun on you?
Yup.
And you let him get away
with that shit?
I know he's a killer.
so I wasn't gonna chance it.
What the fuck you want?
I wanna make you
a job offer. little nigga.
What? Nigga. fuck you.
Hey. be cool. shorty.
This real bread.
Now. check it out.
What I gotta do?
I want you
to be my eyes and ears.
Nigga. I ain't
no fucking snitch.
What's your name. young man?
- Bakari.
I don't need you to talk
to the cops. Bakari.
I want you to deal
directly with me.
Can you do that?
Hurry up. little nigga.
We don't got all day.
Tense music
I can do that.
That's what I thought.
Let's go.
- Hey. dog. what up?
- What's up?
Ah. shit.
Why you all dressed up?
- Got a new job.
- Doing what?
Some real nigga shit.
Sounds illegal to me.
Hey. I'd rather be doing this
than fucking boosting packages.
I don't fuck with criminals.
You fuck
with your brother. though.
Wait. I-I ain't
mean it like that. Nae.
Nae. I ain't mean it like that.
- Leave me alone. Otis.
- Please.
I can't trust you.
I understand.
I want you to know
that I love you.
And I'm sorry I can't be
the man you need me to be.
What'd you do to Q?
Do you really want me
to tell you?
Are you taking his place
for good?
I don't have a choice.
Yes. you do.
Maybe I don't get
to have a peaceful life.
Somebody's gotta be the bad guy.
Soft music
Davion Farris'
"Tunnel Vision" playing
Tunnel...
Do I look okay?
You look beautiful.
Mm.
Oh.
Dreams and visions
Have finally come true
And it's all 'cause of you
Tunnel vision
Love and loyalty
is what it's giving
That's my mission
Love you the way you want
because I listen
My dreams and wishes
Have finally come true
And it's all thanks to you
Oh...
I never thought we'd be here.
But at the same time.
today feels like
a long time coming.
Darnell. you are old-school.
stubborn.
all the qualities I never knew
I needed in my life.
You're also kind.
hilarious.
and quiet as a cat.
deeply emotional...
all the qualities
I've ever wanted in a partner.
Our love has taught me
that a bond between two people
must be nurtured
and must never be
taken for granted.
I promise to you
that I will nurture
our love forever.
and I will never take you
for granted.
Oh. Jada.
I love you.
That's all I know.
And I know I... messed up
a few times in the past.
But I guess I had to fall down
so I could...
really appreciate
what it feels like
to stand on my own two feet.
And I stand here
before you today
an imperfect man.
And I have no desire
to be perfect.
I just wanna be
the best man I can be.
not just for you...
...but for myself.
Jada.
do you take Darnell Robinson
to be your
lawfully wedded husband.
to have and to hold
from this day forward
for better or for worse.
for richer or for poorer.
in sickness and in health.
until death do you part?
I do.
Darnell Robinson.
do you take Jada Washington
to be your lawfully wedded wife.
to have and to hold
from this day forward
for better or for worse.
for richer or for poorer.
in sickness and in health.
until death do you part?
Oh. you better believe it.
You may kiss your bride.
Come here. baby.
That's my mission
Love you the way you want
because I listen
All my dreams and wishes
Have finally come true
And it's all thanks
To you...
- Yes. y'all!
- Yes!
All my single ladies.
it's about that time.
Come on up and try
to catch this bouquet
or dodge it. whichever makes
sense in your life right now.
Come on. y'all.
Okay!
One... two...
three.
Hey!
Yeah. she caught that.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- There you go. That's you.
- Yeah. Pop.
Yeah. she got that.
Hey. hello.
- We be coming like
- Ooh. ooh. ooh
- Got 'em running like
- Every day and night
- Ooh. ooh. ooh
Really ain't nothing to it
That's how black and blue do it
- We be coming like
- Ooh. ooh. ooh
- Got 'em running like
- Every day and night
- Ooh. ooh. ooh
Really ain't nothing to it
That's how black and blue do it
Got blood on my hands
Busting through
these glass ceilings
Command your respect when
I walk into the building
Blessed if I see
another day. Lord willing
I want justice for my city
and the children
What'd you bring me
out here for?
Don't worry about it already.
Did you enjoy your wedding?
Oh. my gosh. I couldn't have
had a more beautiful backyard.
Yeah. yeah. it was nice.
wasn't it?
It really was.
Well. welcome home.
What?
I know you say
I been cheap all my life.
but I just like saving money.
Saving money for what?
For a moment like this.
You bought us a house?
I just closed on it.
You happy?
Yeah!
Yeah. but you can't
go buying us a house
without showing it to me first.
Well. I just wanted
to surprise you.
But what if I hated it?
Do you?
I don't know!
You gon' show it to me?
- Yeah. I'ma show it to you.
- Give me the tour!
What you waiting for?
Yeah.
I'ma give you a whole tour.
Uh-huh.
And soon as we
get done with the tour...
Uh-huh?
...we gon' christen
every room in the house.
Let's start with the kitchen.
We got all your tulips out here
and the flowers.
You sure do.
You got my peonies.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh. babe!
Mwah!
How you afford this?
I came into some money.
How?
Um. look. I found an investor
for Smokey's.
and they wanna franchise.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
Who is it?
Um...
it's Douda.
Did you not see the video
of him beating somebody's ass?
I did. I did.
And he's the reason
Brandon's dead.
We don't know that.
Why you think Brandon's mom
tried to kill him?
Look. all I know
is that he wants to help me.
he believes in me. and he wants
to help out the business.
Look. I know he ain't perfect.
but I got this.
Cynthia Erivo's "Mama" playing
This is for the lonely ones...
You okay?
I wanna move out.
No.
What she said.
I figured you'd say that.
- Then why'd you ask?
- I'm not asking.
You're not moving out. Kevin.
I wanna get emancipated.
Okay. Kev.
you know I'm usually down
to hear you out.
but I can't rock with you
on this one.
I already signed all the papers.
- You serious?
- Yup.
And I got enough money
for a down payment.
Since you so obsessed
with paying rent.
why don't you pay us some?
Yeah. that's a good idea. baby.
You can start by giving us
a little something
towards the mortgage.
and then. in exchange.
we'll give you
a little more freedom.
That's not enough for me.
I wanna move out... on my own.
The special way they shine
They pour a glow...
Here she come.
Papa. why you in the front?
Just get in the car.
Oh. my God.
- Hey. girl.
- Hey. y'all.
What's up?
107.4 The Storm.
Chicago's best
- for hip-hop and R&B.
- Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
- Is that my song?
- Here's something new.
an emerging local artist
straight from...
Congrats. Ma is ha.
Gotta give all the glory
to God on this one.
Thank you. Papa.
Now turn that shit the fuck up!
Hear me out.
I remember them days
When motive was by any means
Look at me now
Thought it was college.
but music was the only way
- I could get me out
-Oh. my God!
Stayed with them kids
at my mama crib
Missing them classes.
44 absences
Now I'm honor roll.
chasing them checks
I ain't checking no Aspen.
knew it
Victor Taylor has pledged
to put people before politics.
and he means it.
Because of him.
we have a brighter future.
And although
we have a long way to go.
I am honored to stand beside him
every step of the way.
So together.
let's rebuild
the city of Chicago
one brick at a time!
So without further ado.
I am proud to introduce
your future city councilman.
Victor Taylor.
Thank you. everyone.
for being here.
Um. my heart is so full
right now.
I'm so grateful to you all.
You know what?
I had a whole speech planned
for you tonight. but...
I think I wanna speak
from the heart
if that's okay.
The truth is...
...Tierra and I...
are not in love.
We're not even a real couple.
The relationship was fabricated
for the campaign.
I wanted y'all to think
that I was a good Black man.
I wanted to be someone
that you could believe in.
But along the way. I. uh...
...forgot who I was.
I can't stand up here and claim
to be anything but human.
I'm a person that is trying
to be his best self
every day.
And I wanna help people.
even though that's-that's not
always rewarded.
So today...
I'm officially announcing
my candidacy for city council.
and I'm not gonna pretend
to be something
or someone I'm not
just to get your votes.
And I also want you to know
that I have recently
fallen in love.
And I hope that she and I can
build a beautiful life together
based on truth and commitment
to pouring into our community.
Until then.
I'll see you
on the campaign trail.
where I hope that you can get
to know me...
the real me.
Thank you.
Montana of 300's
"Undertaker" playing
I'm gonna be...
I'll put in that work
Young nigga living his dreams
I came out them trenches
like Sting
Remember them days when
I used to sit on them swings
And watch niggas
dealing to fiends
They served to my mama. wish
I had a burner to pop 'em
You don't know
the feeling it brings
I feel like the Hulk. I used
to have rips in my jeans
But I had to get to the green
I swallowed the odds because
I'm anointed with God
The devil can't get in between
Gripping my chrome
while I sit on my throne
Tell them niggas come on.
ain't no killing the king
You'll die in the summer
For talking that shit
in the spring
So fall down
like you sipping that lean
If you ain't from here.
you the visiting team
You gon' leave in a stretcher
Ain't no limousine. huh
Brace yourself for the truth
It may hurt a bit
The good thing about pain
is. you learn from it
Make sure your desire
survives through the fire
The disappointment
and discouragement
Better move like you know
what your purpose is
Never say die. learn to fly
through that turbulence
Stop placing the blame.
you say it's God's
But really. you don't know
who word it is
Gotta know who the serpent is
Know they oppress us
That bitch got more game
than a tournament
And the church is the platform
The preacher that's programmed
Gets paid to perform
at the services
If it ain't ether. cancel it
Verses ain't tampered with
Rap god and my word is permanent
I pack heat in my head
like a perm in it
So you know how I roll
like a Percocet
One thing for certain is.
whoever purchased this
Gon' say it's worth it.
he murdered it
Don't forget so we know
what we working with
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm